<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fitness Application</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_throw_app">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_exercise">Exercise</string>
    <string name="title_progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="title_about">About App</string>
    <string name="jumping_jacks">A jumping jack, also known as a star jump and called a side-straddle hop in the US military, is a physical jumping exercise performed by jumping to a position with the legs spread wide and the hands going overhead, sometimes in a clap, and then returning to a position with the feet together and the arms at the sides.</string>
    <string name="high_step">Step and high-step workouts have a variety of fitness benefits. They offer a good cardiovascular workout that’s not repetitious like jogging on a treadmill or using an elliptical machine can be. Plus, there’s a certain “fun” factor to doing a step workout – the music and the constantly changing movements are never dull. It almost makes you forget you’re exercising! Plus, step workouts tone your buttocks and thighs by targeting your hamstrings, quadriceps, and glutes better than most forms of cardiovascular exercise.</string>
    <string name="mountain">The Mountain Climber is a bodyweight exercise that serve as a great full-body workout. This plyometric plank movement does it all: increases core strength, defines the shoulders, chest and upper back, works the quads and glutes -- all while raising the heart rate.</string>
    <string name="flutter">A Flutter Kick is an exercise that specifically targets the lower abdominal wall. You perform this move by lying on your back and using your core to “flutter” your legs up and down. You’ll often see this type of move performed in Pilates, barre and strength training classes.</string>
    <string name="heel">Step 1: Lay down with your back on the ground and your knees bent and pointed towards the ceiling. \nStep 2: With your arms on your side raise your shoulders slightly off the ground. \nStep 3: Using your abs rotate your right hand down to your right foot and then back up. \nStep 4: Then do the same thing with your left hand. \nStep 5: Alternate back and forth for the desired amount of repetitions.</string>
    <string name="legs">STEPS\n 1. Lie on your back, legs straight and together. \n 2. Keep your legs straight and lift them all the way up to the ceiling until your butt comes off the floor. \n3. Slowly lower your legs back down till they’re just above the floor. Hold for a moment. \n4. Raise your legs back up. Repeat.</string>
    <string name="reverse">The reverse crunch is an intermediate level variation of the popular abdominal crunch exercise. Your upper body remains on the mat as you contract your abs to draw your legs towards your chest. It exercises the full length of the rectus abdominis muscle (the six-pack muscle), getting to the deep lower abs.﻿ This bodyweight exercise is easy to add to any abdominal or core workout or use as part of a total body workout.</string>
    <string name="plank">The plank exercise is an isometric core exercise that involves maintaining a position similar to a push-up for the maximum possible time.Lying on the ground with the elbows in line with the shoulder and the feet shoulder width apart, Push your body up bearing the weight on the forearms and feet, Keeping your body straight.</string>
</resources>